[{"answer": "I don't want them! Get rid of them! I don't want to see them", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "We'll take these miserable whelps on an outing, alright! We'll take them to the zoo... WHERE THEY WILL STAY", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "He's not a peeler..", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No... I don't think so", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What happened", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "He must have taken quite a fall", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yes... Well, I want you to clear up a little mess, a breakfast tray was spilt. And bring up another breakfast. When you've done that, you and I shall give the man a bath. But, my friend, I'm counting on your many years of experience to get you through this, Above all, do not scream, do not cry out, or in any way show this man that you are frightened of him..", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yes... Yes, let's go in", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What's all this, then", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Elephant Man", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Hello..", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "My... name is..", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "My... name is..", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend... my frien", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well sir, perhaps I should explain..", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I don't agree. No one can make a reasonable decision about this man's future without at least meeting him. No doctor would presume to diagnose a patient he had never met", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well, I wasn't sure whether he was parroting me because that's all he was capable of, or whether he sensed that that's all I wanted to hear, and he was trying to please me", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "He is. I mean, I've always thought he was. I think he must be. Is he simple? Or is that just something I've wished upon him to make things simpler for myself", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "The Lord is my shepherd, I shall not want, he maketh me to lie down in green pasture", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Righteousness for his namesake", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "How are you feeling today", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I'm feeling very fit, thank you. How is your bronchitis", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I feel much better. Thank you for asking. And you", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I feel much better. Thank you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Good evening. How are you feeling", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Very well, thank you. I have something for you, my friend. I'm sure you'll enjoy it, it's very popular", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Mr. my friend says that you are in the theatre. Do you live there", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Well, even to work there would be wonderful. Is it beautiful", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Why, Mr. my friend, you're not an Elephant Man at all..", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Oh no... no... you're a Romeo", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "How blind of me. Is there anything else, my friend, anything at all that I could get for you", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Please my friend, it would give me so much pleasure to give you something. Something just for yourself. Isn't there something you would like to have", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "O fair my friend, if you will love me soundly with your French heart, I will be glad to hear you confess it brokenly with your English tongue. Do you like me, my friend", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "An angel is like you, my friend, and you are like an angel", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "O bon Dieu! les langues des hommes sont pleines de tramperies", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Oui, dat de tongues of de mans is be full of deceits", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Yes my friend", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " No, my friend, not one that I can see", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " No, my friend, not one that I can see", "docId": "Elephant-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "No, no, I wouldn't change a thing", "qsentId": 40}]